const STORE = [
  {
    question: 'What is the proper term for a group of kittens?',
    answers: ['A kaboodle', 'A Kine', 'A kittle', 'A litter'],
    correctAnswer: 'A litter',
  },
  {
    question: 'All cats are born with what color eyes?',
    answers: ['Blue', 'Yellow', 'Black', 'Green'],
    correctAnswer: 'Blue',
  },
  {
    question: 'What percentage of a cats bones are in its tail?',
    answers: ['10%', '20%', 'None', '50%'],
    correctAnswer: '10%',
  },
  {
    question:
      'What year was the first major cat show held in the United States?',
    answers: ['1950', '1895', '1926', '1778'],
    correctAnswer: '1895',
  },
  {
    question: 'What breed of cat has a reputation for being cross-eyed?',
    answers: ['Persian', 'Himalayan', 'Siamese', 'Egyptian Mau'],
    correctAnswer: 'Siamese',
  },
  {
    question: 'What is the largest breed of cat?',
    answers: ['British Shorthair', 'Savannah', 'Maine Coon', 'Ragdoll'],
    correctAnswer: 'Maine Coon',
  },
  {
    question: ' How many teeth does an adult cat have?',
    answers: ['32', '36', '24', '30'],
    correctAnswer: '30',
  },
  {
    question: 'How fast can cats run?',
    answers: ['40 MPH', '30 MPH', '50 MPH', '20 MPH'],
    correctAnswer: '30 MPH',
  },
  {
    question: 'How did ancient Egyptians mourn when a family cat died?',
    answers: [
      'Throw a party',
      'Shave their eyebrows',
      'Not eat for three days',
      'Sacrifice a dog',
    ],
    correctAnswer: 'Shave their eyebrows',
  },
  {
    question: 'What breed of cat has no tail?',
    answers: ['Singapura', 'Snowshoe', 'La perm', 'Manx'],
    correctAnswer: 'Manx',
  },
];
